{
    "id": "b1a8e45361b94c59afb2f5cd2657d20f",
    "title": "Modification of Nouns | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3b46516735be4a779a426fb4e7e163e4",
            "title": "Modification of Nouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You are ............................ a nuisance.",
                    "description": "We can use quite or rather before an article + singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "quite",
                        "rather",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The film was ..................................",
                    "description": "We use rather before article + singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a rather success",
                        "rather a success",
                        "rather success"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... a singer is he?",
                    "description": "Before a singular countable noun we can use a quantifier with of. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "How much",
                        "How much of a",
                        "How much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think he is .................................",
                    "description": "We can use a quantifier with of before a singular countable noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "bit of a fool",
                        "a bit of a fool",
                        "a bit fool"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was ................................... than a party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more of an informal meeting",
                        "more an informal meeting",
                        "more of informal meeting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ................................ politician than an activist.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more a",
                        "more of a",
                        "more"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is .............................. an intellectual.",
                    "description": "We can use a quantifier with of before a singular countable noun.  A lot is not used in the structure. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a lot of",
                        "very much of",
                        "very much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................. do you want a holiday?",
                    "description": "Questions about degree are asked with how much.",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "How well",
                        "How much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You made ................................ mistakes.",
                    "description": "Quite a few has a similar meaning to rather a lot.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather a lot",
                        "quite a few",
                        "quite few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met ............................. people who spoke German.",
                    "description": "We use few with countable nouns we use little with uncountable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather few",
                        "rather little",
                        "very little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ate ................................ meat.",
                    "description": "Too much can be modified by much and rather. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "much too much",
                        "quite too much",
                        "rather too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We do ............................. of business in China.",
                    "description": "A lot can be modified by quite and rather. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "quite a lot",
                        "quite lot",
                        "much a lot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}